<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our work on SOUTHEN</title>
    <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our work on SOUTHEN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://south-en.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Procedures and Standards</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/implementation/</guid>
      <description>We work with your team to adjust Project Controls and risk management processes, procedures and standards.
Do not start from scratch: We provide and quickly implement processes, procedures and templates, including state-of-the-art business intelligence tools.
Management culture: We help your contractors and subsidiaries to meet your parent company&amp;rsquo;s management systems needs.
Project constrains: We help you identify and implement the adjustments that specific projects conditions make necessary in your management systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Control set up</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/setup/</guid>
      <description>We help your team to quickly develop the project structure and management instruments necessary to make informed decisions.
   Work, Cost and Risk Breakdown Structures (WBS, CBS, RBS).     Project Control Plan (CPC).     Schedule and Basis of Schedule (BOS) development.     Support for Project Execution Plan (PEP) development.     Reporting and deliverables templates.     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project control Management</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/management/</guid>
      <description>We provide direct Project Control Management assistance to new and existing teams to get your projects back on track.
 Regular Project Control Management services. Support new teams in their landing process. Skills evaluation in the Project Control staffing process of your company.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantitative Risk Analysis</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/qra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/qra/</guid>
      <description>Risk sessions facilitation, modelling, and Monte Carlo simulation for portfolios, projects and critical milestones.
   Completion probabilities, P50, P80. Estimate the contingencies required for your projects.     Sensitivity analysis. Evaluate mitigation measures.     Deep-dive analysis for key drivers.     Influence of rare risk events. Analyse outliers&#39; potential impact.     Implementation of proprietary SaaS, vcubo.      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
