<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our work on SOUTHEN</title>
    <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our work on SOUTHEN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://south-en.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Procedures and Standards</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/implementation/</guid>
      <description>We work with your team to adjust Project Controls and risk management processes, procedures and standards.
Do not start from scratch: We provide and quickly implement processes, procedures and templates, including state-of-the-art business intelligence tools.
Management culture: We help your contractors and subsidiaries to meet your parent company&amp;rsquo;s management systems needs.
Project constrains: We help you identify and implement the adjustment that specific projects conditions make necessary in your management systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Controls set up</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/setup/</guid>
      <description>We provide standard high-level descriptive analytics at no charge. Customization and deep-dive options are available.
   Projects&#39; delay distribution.     Distributions decomposition by uncertainty and impact of risks.     High-level risks and historical influence of variables in projects performance.     Descriptive analysis of risks and uncertainty at lower levels (custom).     Statistics and level of confidence (custom).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project controls team</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/management/</guid>
      <description>Custom predictive analytics for portfolios, projects and critical milestones. Take advantage of a rich and transversal database.
   Adjusted level of confidence for distribution fits.     Completion probabilities, P50, P80.     Sensitivity analysis.     Deep-dive analysis for key drivers.     Influence of rare risk events.     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive analytics</title>
      <link>https://south-en.github.io/services/qra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://south-en.github.io/services/qra/</guid>
      <description>To reduce bias in the decision-making process, we are developing vcubo.ai, an AI agent trained with the inputs and results of the decisions taken in past projects.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
